RENE GOLDIN

Email: renegoldin1@gmail.com | Skype: r.goldin | Contact number: 065 941 9712 | Address: San Carlo, St Johns Road, Sea Point, Cape Town | RSA ID number: 841107 0290 086

SUMMARY

A pragmatic team player who excels in creative and structured organisations. I've used my BTech Marketing degree in various capacities and continue to develop my skillsets. I use my coordinating skills to bring a thoughtful perspective to productive work spaces. From working in small, growing companies, to fast-paced agencies and educational environments, I enjoy developing content, and processes to accomplish tasks. I thrive on diverse experiences and growing into new roles.

EXPERIENCE

March 2019 - June 2019

Operations Administrator

(Maternity leave cover 3-month contract)
Pedersen and Lennard | Cape Town, South Africa

- Actively implemented processes to manage production to improve productivity
- Managed the day-to-day logistics of the production on Google sheets
- Communicated with clients and suppliers, and conducted general administrative tasks

October 2017 - March 2019

Executive Assistant to the Managing Director

New Media I Cape Town, South Africa

- Proactively managed the schedules and tasks of the MD of a fast-paced agency
- Prepared documents and board reports for Media24 and other stakeholders
- Coordinated travel, training sessions, and events for the company
- Created PowerPoints and agendas for monthly company sessions and meetings

April 2016 - August 2017

English Language Instructor

Sogang Language Program (SLP) Kindergarten and After- school Education 1 Busan, South Korea

- Interviewed and trained new instructors to comply with SLP teaching methods
- Assessed students writing and speaking abilities for reports
- Developed second language students' English abilities through stimulating and outcome-focused content

April 2015 - April 2016

Adult Program Coordinator & Instructor

Gyeonggi English Village I Paju, South Korea

- Developed specialised adult programmes to client's briefs
- Managed a team of 10 instructors from U.S, South Korea and Australia
- Evaluated programmes through research and consultations with stakeholders, and implemented changes when needed

October 2012 - April 2015

ESL Teacher for Adults and Young Learners

Gyeonggi English Village I Paju, South Korea

- Researched, developed and prepared interactive English lessons
- Collaborated on curriculum development and assisted process to completion
- Trained new staff members and evaluated performances

September 2010 - August 2012

Marketing, Sales and Customer Service

World Gaia Trading and the Green Shop I Hout Bay, Cape Town, South Africa

- Generated new sales and maintained relationships with customers
- Updating promotional material such as brochures and instore displays
- Sourcing solutions for clients and general administrative tasks

June 2008 - January 2010

Online Content Editor

Entertainment Website WhatsOn.co.za I Cape Town, South Africa

- Compiled, updated and edited online content daily through a CMS
- Liaised with stakeholders to coordinate weekly promotions
- Maintained and increased the sites users and page impressions through marketing efforts

EDUCATION

2007 Bachelor of Technology (BTech) Marketing

Cape Peninsula University of Technology I Cape Town, South Africa

2003 National Matric Certificate with Merit

Herzlia High School I Cape Town, South Africa

FURTHER DEVELOPMENT

August 2019 The Web Developers Bootcamp

Udemy Online Course

Provided a foundation for HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Node

January 2019 Learning Digital with Google

Google Programme, Digital skills for Africa

April 2014 The Advanced Creative Writing Online Course

South African Writers College, South Africa

August 2012 TESOL 120 Hour Certificate

Cape Town School of English/ TESOL Training Institute, Cape Town, South Africa

Included coursework and teaching practicum

COMPUTER SKILLS AND OTHER EXPERIENCES

Microsoft Office and Google docs

South African driver's licence (Code B)

English (Fluent) Afrikaans (Basic)

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Node (Basic)
- Articulate Storyline (Basic)

AREAS OF INTEREST

Content Creation and Management

Web Development

Social Change

Project Management

Travel

Education

REFERENCES

Genevieve Train (2019)

Office Manager
Pedersen + Lennard
021 447 2020
info@pederesenlennard.co.za

Aileen Lamb (2017 - 2019)

Managing Director New Media 082 729 8657 aileen.lamb@newmedia.co.za

Cheryl Bridgens (2017 -2019)

Operations Manager
New Media
082 461 1344
cheryl.bridgens@newmedia.co.za

Bianca Prins (2017 – 2019)

Account Manager (Food Division)
New Media
071 896 8622
bianca.prins@newmedia.co.za

May Kim (2015 -2017)

Programme Manager
Sogang Language Program Gaegeum
+82 10 8544 1067 (South Korea)
ecaros0912@naver.com

Jessica Lee (2012 - 2015)

Human Resource Manager Gyeonggi English Village +82 31 956 2500 (South Korea) hr.manager.gev@gmail.com

Greg Walton (2010 - 2012)

Former Company Owner World Gaia Trading 083 629 7986 greg@misolar.co.za